Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Oral History Collection OH.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Oral History Collection
1962-1994
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
OH.019
1 Linear Feet 1 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Collected by the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives; dates unknown. The accession number associated with this collection is 1979.015.
Scope and Contents
See BobCat, NYU's library catalog (http://bobcat.nyu.edu), for a description of this collection. Index available in repository.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
- Patricia Adkins; Union evolution from the 60s to the 80s, Nov 18, 1980; cuid274 (Box 2, Cassette 8)
  General
  Release form YES Summary available
- Walter Bailen, undated
  Release form YES Notes available
- Leon Becker; March on Washington, the Red Scare, Frank Cherry, Mar 11, 1980 (Box 2, Cassette 1, 21A-B)
  Release form YES
- Carl Butler; African-Americans in the union, lack of women in union negotiations, Mar 24, 1988; cuid275 (Box Access CD Box 1, Cd 44A-B, Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 44 A-B)
- Henry Cannon; Evolution of union politics since 1946, Nov 4, 1980 (Box 2, Cassette 4)
- Nick Carnes, Mar 1, 1982 (Box 2, Cassette 22A-C)
- Morris Doswell, Dec 2, 1980 (Box 3, Cassette 37A-B)
- Hy Drucker, Aug 19, 1982 (Box 2, Cassette 23)
- Frank Engleberg, May 20, 1982 (Box 3, Cassette 38)
- Executive Council Meeting, Oct 12, 1982; cuid276 (Box Access CD Box 1, Cd 29A-B, Box 3, Cassette 29A-BFeiner, Silvia)
- Silvia Feiner; Contractual progress since 1960, union consumer services, Nov 11, 1980 (Box 2, Cassette 2)
  Release form YES Transcript available
- Joe Finn; Pro-1960s militancy, Taft/Hartley class consciousness, minorities in unions, Nov 11, 1980; cuid277 (Box 2, Cassette 3)
- James Hodges; Organizing in McCarthy period, state of democracy in 1965, march on D.C., Nov 18, 1980; cuid278 (Box 2, Cassette 5)
  Release form YES SUmmary available
- J. Johnson & T. Weekly, undated (Box 3, Cassette 33)
- Martin Luther King Memorial, Jan 15, 1971 (Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 50-51)
- Martin Luther King Speech, 1962-1967; cuid279 (Box Access CD Box 1, Cd 46, 47, 48, 49, Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 46-49)
  Scope and Contents
  There is some legacy recorded material detectable underneath the main recording for disc 46 (cuid 279A).
- Sam Neuberger, Oct 13, 1982 (Box 3)
- Ngubo and A. Montoya, undated (Box 3, Cassette 32)
- Jack Paley, Jul 15, 1982; 5 sound discs (cd) (Box 3, Cassette 26A-C)
- Harry Respler; Trade work in the Depression era, Oct 31, 1980 (Box 2, Cassette 7A-B)
  Transcript and SUmmary available
- C. Robinson and J. Lowery, undated; cuid151 (Box 3, Cassette 31)
- Cleveland Robinson (Winston); Members' involvement in meetings, problems and politics in 1950s, Nov 23, 1980 - Jan 7, 1983; cuid152 (Box 3, Cassette 12A-C & 35, Box 2)
  Transcript available
- Gideon Rosenblut, May 19, 1982 (Box 3, Cassette 27A-B)
- Morris Rosenzweig, Jan 27, 1982 (Box 3, Cassette 40A-B)
  Transcript Available
- Pete Stein, Jun 4, 1982 & Dec 9, 1982 (Box 3, Cassette 41A-D)
- M. Stepp and J. Mangone, undated (Box 3, Cassette 34)
- J. Turner and J. Davis, undated (Box 3, Cassette 30)
- Irving Weinstock, Feb 15, 1982 (Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 43 A-B)
- David Livingston, 1994-09-04 (Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 45 A-B)
- Preservation Masters and Access Copies Cassettes #9-13, 24-25, 28, 36-37, 39 (Box 4)
  - Frank Brown, May 11 & Jun 4, 1982 (Box 2, Cassette 10A-B)
  - Al Evanoff, Jul 22, 1984 (Box 3, Cassette 24B-D, Box 2, Cassette 24A)
  - Nollie Harstein, Sep 9 $ Sep 24, 1982 (Box 3, Cassette 39A-B)
  - David Livingston, Dec 4, 1981-Feb 25, 1982 (Box 2, Cassette 9A-H)
  - Milton Reverby, Jan 26, 1981-Jan 4, 1982 (Box 2, Cassette 11A-C)
  - Ed Roth; Formation and evolution of the Camera Club, May 24, 1990 (Box 2, Cassette 13A-B)
    Release form YES Transcript Available
  - Bernie Stephens, Apr 1983 (Box Shared Tamiment Cassette Box 1, Cassette 42B, Box 3, Cassette 28A-B)
  - Zeke Cohn, undated (Box 3, Cassette 36A-B)
- Transcripts: Bailen-Roth (Box 5)
- MLK Tapes includes Master CDs (Box 1)